my god
I didn't tell you
there is time to order 1 stop
bye bye people
thank you thank you rafa
ah I got my warm one
Kitchen aunts are very sweet
vei doesn't want me to leave
is on
came before I go buy 1 deal for you
oh that
but you don't have to worry about anything
I can't film you guys here
that's what I talk about brother relationship
far beyond 1 sale it creates Cara
people care about you
is on
it's guys
is the following bro
I'm here now in the center
shop shop barge
is on
it seems like just yesterday that I was here in this store
working as a speaker
now i'm here saying goodbye you know
how are you
you're stylish eh
I'll give you 1 merry christmas and for everything
Probably cleaning this window here old
just clean the window there girl
ha ha ha
actually i came
I came to say goodbye
goodbye merry christmas
buy an egg there
that's it bro
I took the day to say goodbye to the crowd
I'm sick if I can't say goodbye to someone
is on
ha ha it's good
stay with god brother
merry christmas my brother
thank you
that day there
tamo together
let's see you hand
if you notice
every encounter you have in your life is a farewell
maybe the person next to you
having a coffee you never
more can see in life man
I'm leaving
I don't know if I'll see these people anymore
but I'm going there
say goodbye
thank you speak
really care about people man
we need to be more interesting
and less interested
was the first store I cleaned a shop window
and look at the coincidence
hand from Cocoa Show
and then all good so thank god
oh thank you from the bottom of my heart man
caraca hand
she'll give me a basket bro
my god
i don't believe it
top of the sky
Debora pancakes
the cream can
O of the heart
sees it all right
it's not too
our people
look at this bro
Deborah told me
O Cayon
when you leave
pass here in Cocoa kiss the girls
but i was genuine brother
and then the person separated a basket for me
bro doesn't cry caion
don't cry
hand
At the time,
the Caio phone is ringing
all right
wait for your return
my god